Guide to The KZSU Collection ARS.0062
Archive of Recorded Sound
KZSU Collection
1968
ARS.0062
KZSU
1 box :22 7" open reel tapes
Archive of Recorded Sound
The KZSU Collection consists of recordings of a Stanford faculty lecture series sponsored by Century 21 realtors in 1968, originally broadcast on student radio station KZSU.
Access
Open for research; material must be requested at least two business days in advance of intended use. Contact the Archive for assistance.
Scope and Contents
The KZSU Collection consists of tape recordings of lectures by Stanford faculty on campus from January to May 1968, originally broadcast on student radio station KZSU. While on a variety of topics, contemporary sociological, scientific, and economic issues are prevalent. The lecture series was sponsored by Century 21 realty company. Notecards describing tape speed, playback issues, and sound quality are inserted in each tape box. Some of the multi-part lectures are missing a part. Additional recordings may be added to this collection at a later time.
Related Archival Materials
For other KZSU-affiliated recordings, the Archive of Recorded Sound also holds the Stanford Speech Collection, ARS.022. In addition, Stanford University Library Special Collections holds several collections related to the radio station.
Indexing Terms
KZSU (Radio station: Stanford).; Stanford University.; Speeches, addresses, etc.
- I. Century 21 Lectures, 1968; 22 7" open reel tapes
  - Rationality: Individual and Society - Kenneth Arrow, 1968-04-16; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 1)
  - Challenges of Humanistic Psychology - James Bugental, 1968-02-21; 2 7" open reel tapes (Audio 1)
  - The Physical Environment of Man - Charter 2/2, 1968-04-11; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 1)
  - Plato's Republic - Bruce Franklin, 1968-01-02; 2 7" open reel tapes (Audio 1)
  - Alternative Futures For Education in America - Willis Harman 1/2, 1968-04-03; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 1)
  - Some Recent Developments in Brain Research and Biochemistry - David Krech, 1968-01-23; 2 7" open reel tapes (Audio 1)
  - Joshua Lederberg, 1968-01-16; 2 7" open reel tapes (Audio 1)
  - University of the Future - William Linville 2/2, 1968-05-07; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 1)
  - Artificial Intelligence and Creativity - John McCarthy, 1968-01-30; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 1)
  - Dr. Meier, 1968-04-23; 2 7" open reel tapes (Audio 1)
  - Technology and Developing Nations - Eugene Staley 2/2, 1968-05-14; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 1)
  - Monitoring Public Opinion - Philip Stone, 1968-05-16; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 1)
  - Computers in Education - [Patrick] Suppes, 1968-02-06; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 1)
  - Ethical Issues In Future Medicine - E. Fuller Torrey, 1968-01-24; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 1)
  - Values and the Humanities - Virgil Whitaker, 1968-04-02; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 1)
  - The Future of The Family As an Institution - Morris Zelditch, 1968-02-27; 2 7" open reel tapes (Audio 1)